const quizQuestions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "wHO aRe YoU?",
    answers: {
      a: "YES, WHALEN HERE",
      b: "MR. HENRIQUES",
      c: "SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS",
      d: "NON NOOB",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Yes",
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "What is the best shoe?",
    answers: {
      a: "Vans",
      b: "Crocs",
      c: "Socks & Sandals",
      d: "My bare toes",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Crocs",
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "How do you fly?",
    answers: {
      a: "Extremely built up flatulence",
      b: "Airplane",
      c: "My inner chicken",
      d: "Helicopter",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Extremely built up flatulence",
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "Do you like free stuff?",
    answers: {
      a: "No",
      b: "Only if it's on sale",
      c: "Yes",
      d: "YES",
    },
    correctAnswer: "YES",
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: "What is the best way to cut your bagels?",
    answers: {
      a: "Halves",
      b: "Thirds",
      c: "Quarters",
      d: "I chomp it whole",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Quarters",
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "When eating a bowl of cereal, what do you pour first?",
    answers: {
      a: "Milk",
      b: "Cereal",
      c: "Both because I'm an expert multitasker",
      d: "Spoon",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Milk",
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "What is the best breakfast?",
    answers: {
      a: "Green Eggs & Ham",
      b: "Red Eggs & Spam",
      c: "Oatmeal",
      d: "Untoasted toast, Choi style",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Oatmeal",
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "Do you know how to use chopsticks?",
    answers: {
      a: "Yes, um duhh",
      b: "No",
      c: "Only one singular chopstick",
      d: "That's racist",
    },
    correctAnswer: "No",
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: "Do you eat or drink soup?",
    answers: {
      a: "Slurrrppp",
      b: "Drink",
      c: "Eat",
      d: "Nonstop chug",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Slurrrppp",
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: "Hey, you've got something on your shirt - ",
    answers: {
      a: "WOOP!",
      b: "DONE GOOFED!",
      c: "BAHAHAHA!",
      d: "That's embarassing",
    },
    correctAnswer: "WOOP!",
  },
  {
    number: 11,
    question: "Can you ride a bike?",
    answers: {
      a: "I am Karen Choi",
      b: "hard pass",
      c: "Yes",
      d: "Duh",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Yes",
  }
];

const noobAlertGIFS = [
  "https://i.postimg.cc/d17DFwPg/massive-Noob-Alert.gif",
  "https://i.postimg.cc/s2mG1Sgd/banananoob.gif",
  "https://i.postimg.cc/wMP9wjMf/obama-Noob-gif.gif",
  "https://i.postimg.cc/52yRxSPC/amateur-Noob.gif",
  "https://i.postimg.cc/4xHQLLLB/cool-Beans.gif",
];

export { quizQuestions, noobAlertGIFS };
